CAREER OBJECTIVE

Looking forward for a challenging career opportunity in the field of web development, where I can utilize my skills to their fullest potential and gain valuable experience in the nuances of web development. I believe that such an opportunity would be mutually beneficial for both myself and the organization.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web: HTML,CSS

Scripting Languages : JavaScript, React

Framework : Bootsrap

Tools : Visual Studio code, Microsoft Office

SUMMARY OF EXPERIENCES

- Working on frontend development projects using React JS.
- Possessing a strong knowledge of JavaScript concepts.
- Working as Shift Engineer, Maintaining Rotary and Recipocatory Machine parts...
- Organized, flexible and a quick learner with the ability to work independently or in a team, with great interpersonal and leadership qualities.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

• Web Development Intern at PCS Software Solutions, Surandai. November 2022 - Present

ROLE	Web Development Intern
DURATION	8 Months
RESPONSBILITY	Managed and oversaw the React project,
	ensuring its continued functionality and
	optimization

• Shift Engineer at Krishna Mines Super White, Tirunelveli. July 2020 - December 2021

ROLE	Shift Engineer
DURATION	18 Months
RESPONSBILITY	Maintaining Rotary Machine Components in
	optimum Working conditions

• **Graduate Engineering Trainee** at Sundaram Hydraulics Ltd, Sriperumpudur. May 2018 - March 2020

ROLE	Graduate Engineering Trainee
DURATION	22 Months
RESPONSIBILITY	Capturing OEE and Conducting Shift
	Assembly Meeting

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- **BE** in **Mechanical Engineering** studied at S.V.C College of Engineering and Technology (2014-2018), Puliangudi, Tirunelveli with CGPA of 7.48.
- **HSC** (+2) studied at Baren Bruck Higher Secondary School(2014), Surandai with an overall aggregate of 82.75%.
- **SSLC** (**10th**) studied at Baren Bruck Higher Secondary School, Surandai with an overall aggregate of 88%.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name : Ganesan A

Mother's Name : Selvarathi G

Nationality : Indian

Date of Birth : 1-February-1997

Languages Known : Tamil, English

Permanent Address : 13/4/116, 4th Street,

Surandai, Tamilnadu-627859